Unit four. mooncake. mooncake. shelf. shelves. shelf. shelves. rose. rose. shape. glue. glue. fold. fold. complete. complete. DIY.
do it yourself. DIY.
do it yourself. crazy. crazy.
Be crazy about.
Be crazy about. born. born. handyman. handyman. handyman. handyman. power cut. power cut. pipe. pipe. fill with. fill with. unlucky. unlucky. course. course. mess. mess.
in a mess.
in a mess. board. board. lamp. lamp.
catch one's eye. surprise. impossible. paint. can. everywhere. chalk. mark. mark. brush. brush. instructions. instructions. dangerous. dangerous. usual. usual. tie dye. tie tie. tie. string. string. dye. dye. untie. untie. method. method. product. product.
not only, but also.
not only, but also. workshop. workshop. dry. dry. pattern. pattern. reduce. reduce. waste. waste. joy. joy. glove. glove. finger. finger. button. button.